
- Good afternoon, Olivia 
- Want to make new friends and save money while staying at hotels? Just let me know where and when you’re going, and I’ll show you potential roommates and available hotels. It’s that simple! 
- Now let’s get to it! I’m ready for you. 
SKRIV “Ok. I’m looking for a hotel in Oslo next weekend.” 
- I love Oslo! Three people are looking for a roommate at Comfort Xpress Central Station. It’s located near the city centre, with only a short walk from the Opera House. At 51 EUR per night (49% discount), it’s a good rate, however all of them are male. Check out their profiles below. 
PROFILE 1
Name: Alexander
City: Los Angeles
Rating: 4,8
Age: 26
Gender: Male
Bio: Film producer, techie and yogi.

PROFILE 2
Name: Daniel
City: London
Rating: 5,0
Age: 32
Gender: Male
Bio: Write stuff, make stuff, eat stuff.

PROFILE 3
Name: Jason
City: New York City
Rating: 3,8
Age: 36
Gender: Male
Bio: Management consultant.

- Would you like to stay with P1, P2 or P3?  
SKRIV “No boys, please.” 
- Meet Emily (28). She is an artist, just like you. Emily is seeking a roommate for Clarion Collection Hotel Folketeateret. You’ll each pay 90 EUR per night (45% discount). The hotel is located at Youngstorget, with a wide range of bars and restaurants in the area. Would you like to stay with her? 
PROFILE 4
Name: Emily
City: Los Angeles
Rating: 5,0
Age: 28
Gender: Female
Bio: Model and actress. @emrata.

- Would you like to stay with her? 
SKRIV “Yes” 
- All right. I’ll let Emily know you’re interested, but she will have to accept you as well. Stay tuned, and cross your fingers. 
- Quick response. Emily likes you as well and your room is booked. You can get may talk to her using the chat in the top right corner. 
- Press (y) and I’ll charge 77 EUR on your payment card. 
